<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>awilliams</title><link>https://awilliams.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on awilliams</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 18:09:41 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awilliams.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spaghetti Squash Lasagna</title><link>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/spaghetti-squash-lasagna/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 18:09:41 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/spaghetti-squash-lasagna/</guid><description>This is a recipe for Spaghetti Squash Lasagna.
It can be prepared ahead of time and stored in the fridge until ready to bake.
Spaghetti Squash Cook 2 Spaghetti Squash.
I like to use the Instant Pot:
Cut squash in half Place both halves in pot with 1 cup of water Cook on high pressure for 8 minutes Quick release Separate and mix.
Once cooled a bit, remove the inside of the squash and place in a large mixing bowl Add 1 or 2 eggs and mix Optional: Add some olive oil, salt, other seasonings Sauce Make a tomato sauce.</description></item><item><title>wifi-presence</title><link>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/wifi-presence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 10:31:11 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/wifi-presence/</guid><description>Presence detection for home automation: awilliams/wifi-presence.
How It runs on a WiFi router and hooks in to the access point software to receive information about when WiFi clients connect and disconnect from the access point. It then publishes those events to an MQTT broker, which can be consumed by home automation software such as Home Assistant.</description></item><item><title>Instant Pot Yogurt</title><link>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/instant-pot-yogurt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 22:40:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/instant-pot-yogurt/</guid><description>This is a recipe for making yogurt using an Instant Pot.
Equipment Ingredients Directions Sterilize Equipment Heat Milk Cool Milk Add Starter Yogurt Incubate Equipment: Instant Pot After a while, the silicon ring in the lid may develop an odor. Consider a separate ring (available cheap on Amazon) only for yogurt. I&amp;rsquo;ve read that baking the silicon ring in an over can remove odors (unverified).</description></item><item><title>RPI3 Disable LEDs</title><link>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/rpi-no-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 19:10:31 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/rpi-no-leds/</guid><description>To disable the LEDs on a Raspberry Pi 3, add the following to the /boot/config.txt file:
dtparam=act_led_trigger=none dtparam=act_led_activelow=off dtparam=pwr_led_trigger=none dtparam=pwr_led_activelow=off More information: Raspberry Pi Guide - 5.2 Control LEDs</description></item><item><title>RTanque getting started</title><link>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/rtanque-getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 13:12:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://awilliams.github.io/posts/rtanque-getting-started/</guid><description>This is an introduction to RTanque. It covers installation of RTanque and the creation and distribution of a tank. Total time required: ~20min
RTanque is a game for (Ruby) programmers. Players program the brain of a tank and then send their tank+brain into battle against other tanks.
If you are comfortable installing a Ruby gem, run gem install rtanque, and skip to the Making a Tank section.
Some familiarity with the command line and Ruby would be helpful.</description></item></channel></rss>